<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ka Ian Chan</title>
    <link>https://kaian9804.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ka Ian Chan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 15:55:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kaian9804.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Update this Website</title>
      <link>https://kaian9804.github.io/post/07_update_web/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 15:55:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaian9804.github.io/post/07_update_web/</guid>
      <description>Update this Website After adding posts with Hugo, it is need to convert the files as HTML for displaying website.
Go to the GitHub and Hugo file
Start cmd
Enter &amp;ldquo;hugo&amp;rdquo; and press enter
hugo The HTML codes will be generated in the &amp;ldquo;public&amp;rdquo; folder
Copy the codes to the GitHub folder where it can be uploaded via GitHub Desktop
\GitHub\username.github.io The changes will be showed in GitHub Desktop
Write down summary and descriptions of changes, commit to main, and push the changes to GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attending TALE2023</title>
      <link>https://kaian9804.github.io/post/06_tale2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 23:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaian9804.github.io/post/06_tale2023/</guid>
      <description>Go to Auckland One of my conference papers has been accepted by TALE2023. This conference was held in Auckland from 28-Nov to 1-Dec. This is the first time I can attend a conference in person.
Accepted paper: Exploring the Factors and Moderators Influencing the Use of Radar Visualisation of Student Performance from Parents’ Perspective
Attending the Conference I attended the workshop session, keynote and other presentations, and my presentation was scheduled for the last day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating my Website</title>
      <link>https://kaian9804.github.io/post/00_my_web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 01:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaian9804.github.io/post/00_my_web/</guid>
      <description>I want a website I wanted to have my own personal website for a long time. I have tried to create a website many times. I tried to have my own website on 000webhostapp, hostinger and gihub with HTML and CSS, but these designs are usually so simple and unsatisfied for me.
Now I really want to build a new one! I am building this website with Hugo. This is a new way for me to build a website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
